Yes, we will talk about ICICI Lombard's
Q3 numbers here
in the video and will know whether you should make a
new investment in ICICI Lombard
or not. Let's start. So, see,
if we talk about net premium
collection, then
this number is 1
% higher than this in comparison to the previous quarter. And this number is ok. If we
look at it on 200 crores, then there is nothing
here in net premium,
but this profitability has fallen by 28% here.
If we look at this number, it can give a
boost to the market. And this
number is 200 crores, we should
not take this in negative at all
because if we look at the kind of claims that come
daily, if we look at general insurance and
health insurance, the
way the claims of which companies
are big, then due to that, here we can see a chart of
low issues of all the life insurance
companies and health insurance companies
in their ashram. If
we talk about the year, then this
number is 26% higher than this.  Vada, this near
special force revenue numbers are good
but the profitability is one per change is
big and this number has come at 300 crores, if
seen then
from the profitability numbers they can deposit a little market
but the way the
insurance sector has increased due to some of its videos, then in
my opinion
this industry should be on your radar in the coming time, right now
about one and a half to two questions of data
dupatta and
its total time of 1675 is needed, that is
about two and a half hundred rupees, it is trading below its all time high,
if we
look at it percentage wise then it is trading 13 to 14 times below its wanted
MY, see
you will feel in the validation parameters, but the
way their banking is through ICICI Bank
and the way the
bank wants retail deposits and retail loan
growth and you should know
that it is an 11 inches bio product,
so they should not do insurance channel, they are
directly given by God, this is the sex  If
you do not understand this later, then the more easily you understand, the easier it will be to get up.
Now you can understand this business,
how much this business will grow in the coming time,
Rishi, I think it
should be interviewed in the long term, I
am positive, but if it comes to number six now, then
its market will be negative in the entire chapter,
this can make me one, you have to be ready,
you must have come to know everything about the number of ICICI Lombard's customers in pieces, if
you have any query honey, then comment,
I will definitely reply to your comment,
okay friends, thank you, have a nice day.